Xiaoxi
Let's meet.
Then
see you tomorrow.
Let me think.
Your tomorrow,
or my tomorrow?
My tomorrow.
Then I have to wait nine years.
How about at my place?
Well...
Okay.
Your tomorrow.
But I don't know you yet.
Right.
What should we do?
I remember now.
That was in 2016,
on May 6th.
It was really funny.
The food was so good.
Yeah.
Let's meet here again next time.
Alright, sure.
Great, great.
Has everyone got a ride?
We did, we're heading back first.
Bye, bye, bye.
Bye, let's meet next time, bye.
Bye, bye.
Xiaoxi.
Did you get a ride?
Not yet.
But it's fine.
I can wait a bit.
Worst case, I'll walk home.
What about your ride?
My ride is almost here.
Then you should go.
Okay.
Bye, be careful on the road.
Bye.
You creep!
You remember something
from so many years ago so clearly?
You were followed by a creep.
How could I forget?
If that day,
you could have come to be the hero,
we would have met then.
And my impression of you would've soared.
Good idea.
But won't it be dangerous?
What's there to fear?
The creep will trip over the green belt.
Alright.
Wing Chun!
Chen Mo!
Keep your voice down!
Okay.
The food is so good.
Yeah.
Let's meet here again next time, okay?
Sure, great.
Which one is it?
Has everyone got a ride?
We did, we're heading back first.
Bye, bye, bye.
Bye, bye.
Let's meet again next time.
Bye.
Xiaoxi, did you get a ride?
Not yet.
What about your ride?
My ride is almost here.
Then you should go.
Okay.
Be careful, Bella.
Bye.
Bye, bye.
Hello.
Du Xiaoxi.
Where's the creep?
Why are you running so fast?
Why is it so dark here?
Where are you running to?
Green belt!
You creep!
So the creep was you.
And you can still laugh?
My eyes didn't open for three days.
And did you really have to write
fifteen "ha"s on the note?
Sorry, sorry.
But it was worth it.
At least
I got to see you.
Am I like you imagined?
No.
Clearly my imagination
was too limited.
That's so cheesy.
More or less.
The person matches the handwriting.
The handwriting matches the person.
Then your handwriting isn't great.
Don't you think it's amazing?
I want to write our experience
into a novel.
Incorporate what you said,
about how at certain
coordinates in the world,
due to changes in the gravitational field,
causing differences in the flow of time
and the bending of spacetime,
enabling people from two different times
to communicate across time.
That's not good.
Someone already wrote it.
Even though you'd write it before her now,
that's cheating.
I even gave myself a pen name.
Called "Suan Tang". How is it?
How do you know "Suan Tang"?
I don't know.
Then why call yourself "Suan Tang"?
Secret.
And also,
I've already thought of a title.
It will be called
"The First Reunion".
What do you think?
But I still can't write these two days.
The doctor said not to strain my eyes.
I still have to go to
First Hospital for a check-up tomorrow.
I'll come find you.
Where will you find me?
At First Hospital?
Hello?
You called me over in such a hurry.
Is there good news?
What's wrong? Why are you looking at me like that?
I am...
I... I have lost a bit of weight recently.
It's not because...
my book can't get published, is it?
I've been so worried I can't eat anything.
And then...
Are you Suan Tang?
Yes, I am.
Did you write "The First Reunion"?
You... Listen to yourself.
If I didn't write it, who did? You?
Tell me the truth.
I am telling the truth.
Then who is Chen Mo?
You... maybe you should sit down.
My... my brother's room is at the very back.
Suan Tang.
Aishang Yu.
Sis, we have a guest.
Chen Mo.
Who is it?
You... you've got the wrong person.
Is that so?
Then how do you explain this photo?
From 2016.
May 11th.
Because Chen Mo went to the hospital for his eyes.
At the entrance of the First Hospital...
a car lost control.
It crashed into the crowd.
Fortunately...
he was treated in time.
Chen Mo's life was saved.
After that...
he almost never went out.
He almost never went out.
He stayed home and finished writing...
"The First Reunion".
Because of his leg...
he became extremely insecure.
He was afraid to see people.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Especially you.
One...
Boss!
Boss! Boss!
Where's that copy of "One Hundred Years of Solitude" from the bookshelf?
Sold.
Sold it.
Is it strange for a bookstore...
to sell a book?
Then... when did you sell it?
Just now.
Who did you sell it to?
A girl wearing a red hat.
Red hat.
Okay.
Thank you, boss! Thank you!
Red hat...
Wait!
Wait a minute!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I... I mistook you for someone else.
It's... it's fine.
Don't go to the hospital.
Chen Mo!
Don't go to the hospital!
What was that?
If this bookshelf...
is a medium connecting time and space...
then what's on it...
every coordinate point...
every book...
is it possible...
that each one connects...
to a different time and space?
So...
you knew all along.
Who are you, really?
Just an ordinary bookstore owner.
Boss...
Actually...
I've already tried to save Chen Mo...
many times.
I failed every time.
No.
This time, I've found...
a way to save him.
As long as I, on that day...
don't leave a message on "One Hundred Years of Solitude"...
for him...
then everything that followed...
won't happen.
And Chen Mo won't get hurt.
If that's the case...
you two might never...
meet.
It doesn't matter.
Du Xiaoxi.
Although this is a bit hard to believe...
please trust me.
Don't leave a message on "One Hundred Years of Solitude".
Because...
Okay.
As we can see...
the main objectives...
of this event are...
First...
to boost the sales...
of our new book.
Xiaoxi.
Through the impact of the book signing...
Why do you look so listless?
It's nothing.
I just feel like...
I had a very long dream.
But I can't remember any of it.
Right?
Now, the second point...
Xiaoxi.
Here.
Here, Chief Editor.
Do you think you can handle it?
I... I think...
Yes, I can.
Good.
Then tonight at eight...
you go to the bookstore.
Go to that new book signing event...
and assist Pipi.
Any objections?
No.
Chief Editor.
Good. Let's continue.
This definitely counts as overtime.
And whose fault is that?
You ditched the meeting.
Otherwise we wouldn't be here.
You're the best.
You're the only one who'd come with me.
You're buying me a late-night snack later.
Sure.
What's wrong?
Let's go.
It's nothing.
Let's go in.
I thought...
you didn't want to buy me that snack.
What are you talking about?
The book signing is on the second floor.
We still have some time.
You go up first.
I want to look around.
Okay, but be quick.
It's okay.
You... you can... it's fine.
Here you go.
Thank you.